

# Alireza Akrami

# Web Developer

Thalmässing, Germany June 18th, 1989 **akrami.alireza@gmail.com** 

## **SUMMARY**

I am a web developer with almost 8 years of experience which 4 years of that were on web security. I'm experienced in end-to-end development from server setup to design, development, and deployment. I'm seeking a position as a full-stack web developer or similar opportunity, where I can expand my technical knowledge and experience new challenges.

I have a good relationship with my colleagues, customers, and clients. I'm curious, flexible and self-starter with minimal supervision with good communication and cooperation. I am enthusiastic to learn new technologies.

#### **SKILLS**

- Web Development: PHP, Laravel, Symfony, NodeJS, ReactJS, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Sass
- Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis
- Linux: Basic Linux administration and Bash scripting
- Other: Docker, Git, Gitlab CI, API, Nginx, Python
- Soft Skills: Creativity, Responsibility, Teamwork, Time management,
  Communication, Problem solving, Tolerance and Patience

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **BRTech**, Tehran— Full Stack Web Developer

MAY 2019 - PRESENT

- Planned, developed and maintained several web apps from scratch
- Developed the user interface on new web applications using technologies like ReactJS, Sass,

HTML, CSS, and Javascript

- Redesigned web applications to add progressive capabilities
- Implement design team prototypes in the form of web pages
- Worked as a productive and positive team member to design, code, test, report, and debug operations
  - Managed front-end and back-end development
- Successfully identified, diagnosed, and fixed websites' problems on front-end and back-end
- Helped to achieve a consistent look and visual theme across web designs
- Worked well independently and within a team setting

Technologies: PHP, Symfony, Laravel, PostgreSQL, MySQL, NodeJS, MongoDB, Linux, Redis, ReactJS, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Sass, Docker, Git, Gitlab-CI, API, Nginx, Continuous Integration

# BRTech, Tehran— Technical Support Engineer

SEPTEMBER 2018 - MAY 2019

- Managed and maintained over 18 CentOS Linux servers
- Troubleshot services and programs
- Kept service availability up to 99.99%

Technologies: Linux, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis

## **Ansar Bank**, Tehran—Web Developer and Security Specialist

MARCH 2014 - SEPTEMBER 2018

- Pentest and find vulnerabilities on internal websites on different periods of time
- Planned, developed and maintained many web applications with Laravel to aid in the day-by-day tasks. For example a new management system to control the entry/exit of people to SOC/NOC to Increase the ease of physical authentication of users
  - Maintained Fortiweb Web Firewall for new vulnerabilities and rules
- Launched and maintained a Gitlab server, in order to integrate all coding processes on the website
- Worked closely with project managers to ensure that the web applications meet the high security requirements

Technologies: Linux, MongoDB, MySQL, PHP, Laravel, Python, Git, Continuous Integration, WebInspect, ZAP, SQLMap, and Many tools on Kali Linux.

## **Freelance**— Web Developer

2012 - 2014

- Planned, developed and maintained several web projects
- Design and implement production environment for web applications
- Tune and Troubleshoot websites and web applications

Technologies: Linux, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, PHP, Laravel, Python, Git, MySQL

## **EDUCATION**

# **K.N.Toosi University of Technology,** Tehran — *M.Sc. Information Technology*

2012 - 2014

**University of Isfahan,** Isfahan — B.Sc. Information Technology

2007 - 2012

# **LANGUAGES**

English: B2German: B1Persian: Native

# **PROFILES**

My Blog: https://iakrami.ir/en
 Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/iakrami
 Github: github.com/akrami
 Twitter: twitter.com/alirezatech